1
00:02:14,520 --> 00:02:18,199
My work...
My work here is done.

2
00:02:18,200 --> 00:02:20,719
Rats? Put that with the others...

3
00:02:20,720 --> 00:02:23,479
No, no, I... I wanna go.
No, it's your go tomorrow.

4
00:02:23,480 --> 00:02:25,439
No, no, no, it's MY turn!

5
00:02:25,440 --> 00:02:27,439
Hey!

6
00:02:27,440 --> 00:02:29,279
Why are you pouring the water?!

7
00:02:29,280 --> 00:02:31,000
What makes you think it's water?

8
00:02:33,560 --> 00:02:37,160
Ah, what a glorious moment.

9
00:02:37,960 --> 00:02:40,639
Today, I will show the world
how great I am!

10
00:02:40,640 --> 00:02:43,600
Everyone will admire and love me!

11
00:02:53,600 --> 00:02:56,759
I am so very proud
to present to you today...

12
00:02:56,760 --> 00:02:59,719
Who is he talking to?
I don't know. Neither does he.

13
00:02:59,720 --> 00:03:02,719
He's always talking to himself!

14
00:03:02,720 --> 00:03:04,599
Attention, please,

15
00:03:04,600 --> 00:03:07,319
for this very special moment...

16
00:03:07,320 --> 00:03:09,359
RATS!

17
00:03:18,680 --> 00:03:21,800
...the grand opening of the dam!

18
00:03:30,080 --> 00:03:33,199
Ow, look at all that water!
We can be Pirates!

19
00:03:33,200 --> 00:03:35,519
Oh, no, no, no, no...

20
00:03:35,520 --> 00:03:39,439
...we can be Pi-RATS!
Yes!

21
00:03:39,440 --> 00:03:42,359
I wish I'd thought of that!

22
00:03:44,200 --> 00:03:47,720
Perfect. It is absolutely perfect.

23
00:03:48,520 --> 00:03:51,199
Soon, all will be under water,

24
00:03:51,200 --> 00:03:53,599
and my beautiful lodge
will be ready.

25
00:03:53,600 --> 00:03:55,639
The world will be amazed.

26
00:03:55,640 --> 00:03:58,319
I will be praised and loved.

27
00:03:58,320 --> 00:04:00,079
This is...

28
00:04:00,080 --> 00:04:02,719
..my absolute...

29
00:04:02,720 --> 00:04:04,760
...Masterpiece!

30
00:04:05,720 --> 00:04:08,959
Thanks! I wanted
to do something really special

31
00:04:08,960 --> 00:04:11,199
for Seal and Mermaid
before they leave.

32
00:04:11,200 --> 00:04:14,079
It's fantastic!
Dear Friends,

33
00:04:14,080 --> 00:04:16,599
I would like to say a few words...
Oh! It's starting!

34
00:04:16,600 --> 00:04:18,679
Where are Fox and Hare?

35
00:04:18,680 --> 00:04:21,399
Oh! There you are!

36
00:04:21,400 --> 00:04:23,559
Thank you, Fox and Hare,

37
00:04:23,560 --> 00:04:26,479
for throwing us
this great farewell party.

38
00:04:26,480 --> 00:04:28,319
Now, to get the party going,

39
00:04:28,320 --> 00:04:31,839
Mermaid will sing you
- one of her unparalleled songs.
- Ooh!

40
00:04:31,840 --> 00:04:34,719
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you,

41
00:04:34,720 --> 00:04:38,679
the one, the only Mermaid!

42
00:04:38,680 --> 00:04:40,919
Look at me

43
00:04:40,920 --> 00:04:42,999
♪ The Queen of the sea

44
00:04:43,000 --> 00:04:46,799
♪ Born with two legs originally

45
00:04:46,800 --> 00:04:50,799
♪ But since I grew
This Beautiful tail

46
00:04:50,800 --> 00:04:52,839
♪ I'm fast as a dolphin

47
00:04:52,840 --> 00:04:54,919
♪ And sleek as a whale

48
00:04:54,920 --> 00:04:57,079
♪ I have many fans

49
00:04:57,080 --> 00:04:58,999
♪ They all adore me...
Come, Fox.

50
00:04:59,000 --> 00:05:01,800
♪ They worship my voice
They want to be me...

51
00:05:02,680 --> 00:05:04,959
Let's have a little pirate dance!
No!

52
00:05:04,960 --> 00:05:08,279
Come on, Jack! Come on!
Stop it!

53
00:05:08,280 --> 00:05:09,999
No! Stop it!

54
00:05:10,000 --> 00:05:13,479
Enough!
♪ When I sing, my heart si-i-i-ings

55
00:05:13,480 --> 00:05:16,520
♪  ♪
Argh!

56
00:05:17,440 --> 00:05:21,039
Wooh! Argh! Ah!

57
00:05:21,040 --> 00:05:23,000
Woo, hoo, wah!

58
00:05:23,920 --> 00:05:26,919
Help! Water! Water!

59
00:05:26,920 --> 00:05:30,079
Oh! Oh! I know a great party game!

60
00:05:33,800 --> 00:05:35,200
I am gonna get the cake.

61
00:05:40,760 --> 00:05:43,519
Woo-hoo! Ya-hoo!
Yee-ha! Wow!

62
00:05:43,520 --> 00:05:47,159
Whoo! Now me, now me, me, me, me!

63
00:05:47,160 --> 00:05:49,319
O-O-O-Oh!

64
00:05:49,320 --> 00:05:51,159
I am an EXCELLENT slider!

65
00:05:51,160 --> 00:05:53,959
You call that excellent sliding?!

66
00:05:53,960 --> 00:05:57,840
Well, then, you probably haven't seen
my Foxy Super Sliding Moves yet!

67
00:05:59,560 --> 00:06:02,679
Woo-hoo! Oh... ah... ya-hoo!

68
00:06:02,680 --> 00:06:05,879
Wow, what about that then, eh?

69
00:06:05,880 --> 00:06:09,639
Are those your best
Foxy Sliding Moves? Really?

70
00:06:09,640 --> 00:06:12,359
Well, if that's
the best you've got, dear Fox

71
00:06:12,360 --> 00:06:15,719
♪ Then I can beat you in my socks...

72
00:06:15,720 --> 00:06:17,799
♪ Cos you're no Tusk
and lack my skills

73
00:06:17,800 --> 00:06:20,119
♪ Your performance brings no thrills

74
00:06:20,120 --> 00:06:23,799
♪ But my performance is so good
Just see me sliding on ONE foot! ♪

75
00:06:23,800 --> 00:06:27,159
Ooh, yeah! Look at me!
Sliding! Sliding!

76
00:06:27,160 --> 00:06:29,919
Like... Like a new-born lamb.

77
00:06:29,920 --> 00:06:33,119
On one foot!
Sliding! Deal with that!

78
00:06:33,120 --> 00:06:35,159
It's clear
That you think you are hot,

79
00:06:35,160 --> 00:06:37,000
♪ But is that true?
Well, no it is not!

80
00:06:38,120 --> 00:06:40,959
♪ So I will beat you on the spot! ♪

81
00:06:40,960 --> 00:06:44,600
Yes. Well,
I heard that kind of thing before,
but it never happens.

82
00:06:46,680 --> 00:06:49,959
Wooh! Oh!

83
00:06:49,960 --> 00:06:52,759
Look out, Fox! Not that way!

84
00:06:52,760 --> 00:06:54,279
A-A-A-Ah!

85
00:06:57,360 --> 00:07:01,319
Ah! My books... my things...

86
00:07:01,320 --> 00:07:03,360
everything is wet!

87
00:07:04,480 --> 00:07:06,479
My cake!

88
00:07:06,480 --> 00:07:09,039
I just thought the slip
and slide was a fun idea.

89
00:07:09,040 --> 00:07:12,839
It was a CRAZY idea!
Come on.

90
00:07:12,840 --> 00:07:15,719
We'd better start
cleaning right away.

91
00:07:15,720 --> 00:07:18,559
Now? But we're having a party!

92
00:07:18,560 --> 00:07:20,640
Yeah, a party without cake...

93
00:07:21,840 --> 00:07:24,040
It stills tastes really good.

94
00:07:24,840 --> 00:07:26,519
Wait!

95
00:07:26,520 --> 00:07:29,360
Surprise!

96
00:07:31,000 --> 00:07:34,320
Very realistic.
Although my boat is slightly bigger.

97
00:07:35,320 --> 00:07:38,200
It's Hare's cake.
But Fox helped.

98
00:07:39,240 --> 00:07:41,599
How did you get it so moist?

99
00:07:41,600 --> 00:07:44,920
Long story!

100
00:07:50,040 --> 00:07:52,999
Do you really have to go?
Duty calls.

101
00:07:53,000 --> 00:07:55,279
What is a Seal without the sea?

102
00:07:55,280 --> 00:07:58,159
Yes... I can hear the sea calling!

103
00:07:58,160 --> 00:08:01,119
But the sea is
the other way, Mermaid.

104
00:08:01,120 --> 00:08:03,759
Oh, yes, of course!

105
00:08:03,760 --> 00:08:05,839
- Have a safe trip!
- Off we go!

106
00:08:05,840 --> 00:08:07,799
Don't be strangers!

107
00:08:07,800 --> 00:08:10,639
Come back soon!
We'll miss you!

108
00:08:10,640 --> 00:08:13,079
No, we won't!
Jack!

109
00:08:13,080 --> 00:08:15,359
A pirate doesn't say such things.

110
00:08:15,360 --> 00:08:19,159
Ah! Good night.
Have a good night watch, Owl.

111
00:08:19,160 --> 00:08:21,240
Yea, Owl,
have a good night watch.

112
00:08:22,680 --> 00:08:25,439
What a party!

113
00:08:25,440 --> 00:08:29,159
Ahem!

114
00:08:29,160 --> 00:08:32,880
What?
Aren't you forgetting something?

115
00:08:33,760 --> 00:08:36,799
Oh, can't we do it tomorrow?

116
00:08:36,800 --> 00:08:39,320
OK.

117
00:08:40,120 --> 00:08:42,799
Ah.

118
00:08:42,800 --> 00:08:45,000
Good watch, Hoohoo.

119
00:08:46,320 --> 00:08:48,320
Hoo-hoo!

120
00:08:48,520 --> 00:08:50,519
Hoo-hoo!

121
00:08:50,520 --> 00:08:54,280
Are you coming, my little pirate?
No!

122
00:09:00,520 --> 00:09:02,520
It's not comfy.

123
00:09:13,760 --> 00:09:15,999
Hoo-hoo!

124
00:09:19,640 --> 00:09:22,559
Ah? Hm?

125
00:09:27,040 --> 00:09:29,200
What's that...?

126
00:09:33,760 --> 00:09:36,759
- You finish up this last bit.
- Ah!

127
00:09:36,760 --> 00:09:38,960
And I'll do the kitchen.

128
00:09:50,320 --> 00:09:53,159
Oh, no, it's water! Oh!

129
00:09:55,440 --> 00:09:58,239
Ah! Cold!

130
00:09:58,240 --> 00:10:01,119
W-What are you doing?

131
00:10:04,440 --> 00:10:06,439
Fox, Hare!

132
00:10:06,440 --> 00:10:08,319
I see water!

133
00:10:08,320 --> 00:10:11,159
What... What can we do about it?

134
00:10:11,160 --> 00:10:14,119
We'll take care of it. Thanks, Owl!

135
00:10:14,120 --> 00:10:16,399
No, not in here. I mean...

136
00:10:16,400 --> 00:10:19,479
I know, it's everywhere!

137
00:10:19,480 --> 00:10:21,439
Don't worry, leave it to us.

138
00:10:21,440 --> 00:10:23,319
No, listen to me...

139
00:10:23,320 --> 00:10:26,399
It will be fine, Owl.

140
00:10:26,400 --> 00:10:28,319
Just let us finish this.
But, but, but...

141
00:10:28,320 --> 00:10:30,639
Ooh!

142
00:10:30,640 --> 00:10:32,799
What now?

143
00:10:32,800 --> 00:10:34,999
I know! Tusk!

144
00:10:37,120 --> 00:10:39,160
Hm, somebody called me...

145
00:10:41,520 --> 00:10:44,359
Tusk! Tusk! Help!

146
00:10:44,360 --> 00:10:46,719
Yes, I am an excellent helper.

147
00:10:46,720 --> 00:10:48,919
Tusk! Wake up!

148
00:10:48,920 --> 00:10:51,039
You're in the water!

149
00:10:54,920 --> 00:10:57,359
Wake up, wake up, Tusk!

150
00:10:57,360 --> 00:10:59,959
Oh, uff, yes, uff so good...

151
00:10:59,960 --> 00:11:02,639
Wake up, wake up, Tusk!

152
00:11:02,640 --> 00:11:04,680
Oh, harder!

153
00:11:07,000 --> 00:11:09,480
Looks like it's just
you and me, Hoohoo.

154
00:11:13,960 --> 00:11:16,240
No-o-o-o! Ah!

155
00:11:17,920 --> 00:11:21,159
Jack! Jack!
What's going on with all the water?

156
00:11:21,160 --> 00:11:24,720
Hm, don't know, don't care.

157
00:11:27,880 --> 00:11:31,239
Goodnight, Hare.

158
00:11:31,240 --> 00:11:33,480
Sleep well, Fox.

159
00:11:40,800 --> 00:11:42,840
Oh-oh-oh.

160
00:11:44,000 --> 00:11:46,560
Surely, there must be
a simple explanation.

161
00:11:49,240 --> 00:11:52,239
You will see, Hoohoo. Don't worry.

162
00:11:52,240 --> 00:11:54,440
It's only a little...

163
00:11:55,480 --> 00:11:58,360
o-oh...
..water!

164
00:11:59,880 --> 00:12:02,839
Oh, no! Oh, no.

165
00:12:39,440 --> 00:12:41,760
My life's work.

166
00:12:46,200 --> 00:12:49,120
And no one to appreciate
the brilliance of...

167
00:12:49,920 --> 00:12:52,960
...well... of me!

168
00:13:06,760 --> 00:13:08,839
What a wonderful...

Oh!

169
00:13:08,840 --> 00:13:10,879
..day?

170
00:13:10,880 --> 00:13:14,360
Fox!

171
00:13:15,440 --> 00:13:18,079
Fox! What have you done now?

172
00:13:20,240 --> 00:13:23,439
I didn't do...
I haven't done anything!

173
00:13:23,440 --> 00:13:27,199
Wha...? Ah... Wha...?

174
00:13:27,200 --> 00:13:30,920
Oh. Must have been
quite a downpour last night.

175
00:13:33,400 --> 00:13:36,319
Is Owl up already? That's strange.

176
00:13:36,320 --> 00:13:38,480
His bed hasn't been slept in.

177
00:13:40,080 --> 00:13:42,519
Owl?
Where is he?

178
00:13:55,760 --> 00:13:57,800
Huh?

179
00:13:58,680 --> 00:14:01,559
What's this?
Where am I?

180
00:14:01,560 --> 00:14:03,879
Aah! Aah!

181
00:14:03,880 --> 00:14:06,120
Welcome.

182
00:14:08,000 --> 00:14:13,239
Tusk? Tu-u-u-usk?!

183
00:14:13,240 --> 00:14:15,280
What?

184
00:14:16,160 --> 00:14:18,440
You are all muddy!
Am I?

185
00:14:19,440 --> 00:14:21,559
Oh, I am!

186
00:14:21,560 --> 00:14:23,880
Have you seen Owl?
No.

187
00:14:24,720 --> 00:14:28,199
Owl? Owl?

188
00:14:28,200 --> 00:14:30,879
Owl? Where are you?
Owly?

189
00:14:30,880 --> 00:14:33,920
Hoohoo? Where are you?
Owl?

190
00:14:34,760 --> 00:14:38,119
Owl?
Whoops, sorry.

191
00:14:38,120 --> 00:14:41,559
Good morning, Ping Wing!
Is Owl with you?

192
00:14:41,560 --> 00:14:44,719
-  No.
- Why?

193
00:14:44,720 --> 00:14:47,760
Let's keep looking.
What... What... W-What's going on?

194
00:14:49,520 --> 00:14:52,119
HA!
Your money or your life!

195
00:14:52,120 --> 00:14:53,919
I mean it!

196
00:14:53,920 --> 00:14:56,119
Not now, Jack.

197
00:14:56,120 --> 00:14:58,519
Have you seen Owl?

198
00:14:58,520 --> 00:15:00,559
Maybe. Maybe not.

199
00:15:00,560 --> 00:15:02,920
What's it worth to you?

200
00:15:07,560 --> 00:15:10,119
Shouldn't you have saved
a piece for m...

201
00:15:10,120 --> 00:15:12,999
for Owl?
Is it far, Jack?

202
00:15:13,000 --> 00:15:15,440
This is where I last saw him.

203
00:15:16,240 --> 00:15:19,040
But look what I found after!

204
00:15:20,560 --> 00:15:22,959
Come on. See!

205
00:15:22,960 --> 00:15:25,360
What's that?

206
00:15:26,480 --> 00:15:28,679
Where's that lake come from?

207
00:15:28,680 --> 00:15:32,360
Look!
What are you...?

208
00:15:35,200 --> 00:15:37,839
Hoohoo! Oh, no!

209
00:15:37,840 --> 00:15:41,119
Then Owl must be
somewhere out there.

210
00:15:41,120 --> 00:15:44,119
On the water? But water scares him!

211
00:15:44,120 --> 00:15:47,680
I will save him!
For I am an EXCELLENT swimmer!

212
00:15:55,600 --> 00:15:57,679
Uh... Perhaps a little later.

213
00:15:57,680 --> 00:15:59,839
I didn't have breakfast yet.

214
00:15:59,840 --> 00:16:02,239
Don't worry, Hoohoo.

215
00:16:02,240 --> 00:16:04,639
Owl will be back in no time!

216
00:16:04,640 --> 00:16:08,199
We have to look for Owl. But how?...

217
00:16:08,200 --> 00:16:10,719
I know! With a boat.

218
00:16:10,720 --> 00:16:13,919
I have a boat!
Your boat's got a hole in it.

219
00:16:13,920 --> 00:16:17,280
My boat is fine!
Somebody need a boat?

220
00:16:19,000 --> 00:16:21,919
What are you doing here?
The road was blocked with water,

221
00:16:21,920 --> 00:16:25,119
so we had to come back.
Couldn't risk the merchandise to...

222
00:16:25,120 --> 00:16:27,239
Never seen this lake before.
Ooh!

223
00:16:27,240 --> 00:16:30,519
Owl is missing!
And he is somewhere out there!

224
00:16:30,520 --> 00:16:32,319
We have to find him!

225
00:16:32,320 --> 00:16:35,040
I'll look for him! Huh.

226
00:16:36,320 --> 00:16:38,560
Ah! I love a lake.

227
00:16:41,480 --> 00:16:44,599
Owl?
Uh... Good try, Mermaid! Ha.

228
00:16:44,600 --> 00:16:47,640
Have another go!
Owl?

229
00:16:49,120 --> 00:16:51,519
Not sure
this is going to work...

230
00:16:51,520 --> 00:16:54,480
No... Whoa!

231
00:16:56,080 --> 00:16:58,200
But this might.

232
00:17:00,880 --> 00:17:05,079
Ahoy!
Operation Rescue Owl is underway!

233
00:17:05,080 --> 00:17:06,839
Prepare the boat.

234
00:17:06,840 --> 00:17:09,879
Take care, landlubbers!

235
00:17:09,880 --> 00:17:12,399
Anchors away!
Don't worry!

236
00:17:12,400 --> 00:17:15,319
We'll be back as soon
as we can. With Owl.

237
00:17:15,320 --> 00:17:17,479
Be careful!

238
00:17:17,480 --> 00:17:19,720
Owl?

239
00:17:21,960 --> 00:17:24,080
Owl? Oh.

240
00:17:25,160 --> 00:17:27,919
Oh, hello, little friend!

241
00:17:27,920 --> 00:17:31,479
Have you seen Owl? Ah!

242
00:17:31,480 --> 00:17:33,999
Ow!

243
00:17:34,000 --> 00:17:38,000
OK. So you look that way,
we'll look this way.

244
00:17:41,160 --> 00:17:43,160
Owl?!

245
00:17:44,200 --> 00:17:46,200
Where could he be?

246
00:17:49,000 --> 00:17:51,399
So you haven't said anything

247
00:17:51,400 --> 00:17:54,040
about how fantastic
you think my Lodge is. Ha.

248
00:17:55,080 --> 00:17:57,519
In fact, you haven't said
anything at all!

249
00:17:57,520 --> 00:18:01,440
But I can understand,
this must all be a lot to take in.

250
00:18:02,440 --> 00:18:04,799
If I think how great I am...

251
00:18:04,800 --> 00:18:06,840
I become speechless, too!

252
00:18:08,440 --> 00:18:10,439
W-Where's Hoohoo?

253
00:18:10,440 --> 00:18:12,719
Where are my friends?

254
00:18:12,720 --> 00:18:15,600
Friends? Friends, you say.

255
00:18:17,120 --> 00:18:19,399
Hm. Rats!

256
00:18:19,400 --> 00:18:21,879
Pi-rats!...
Already told him...

257
00:18:21,880 --> 00:18:24,359
Go and find Owl's, hm...
"friends" -

258
00:18:24,360 --> 00:18:26,399
whatever they are -

259
00:18:26,400 --> 00:18:28,919
a-and bring them here immediately!
We can do that, can't we?

260
00:18:28,920 --> 00:18:30,959
Ah, yeah, I love a mission, I do.

261
00:18:30,960 --> 00:18:34,199
The more admirers, the better!

262
00:18:39,160 --> 00:18:42,759
Oof!
This lake is so big!

263
00:18:42,760 --> 00:18:45,079
Oof... Don't worry, Hare.

264
00:18:45,080 --> 00:18:47,919
Captain Fox will save the day!

265
00:18:47,920 --> 00:18:50,279
Oh, yeah? How?

266
00:18:50,280 --> 00:18:53,159
Well... uh... I just... um...

267
00:18:53,160 --> 00:18:56,479
We, um...
Ah! You see?!

268
00:18:56,480 --> 00:19:00,000
Hey! Hey! He-e-e-ey!

269
00:19:01,160 --> 00:19:03,039
Rats! Over here!

270
00:19:03,040 --> 00:19:05,719
We're not rats!
We're Pi-rats!

271
00:19:05,720 --> 00:19:07,760
Pi-rats!

272
00:19:08,600 --> 00:19:10,879
Hello! Um.. I am captain Fox!

273
00:19:10,880 --> 00:19:12,839
Did you see an owl...

274
00:19:12,840 --> 00:19:14,920
called... well, Owl?

275
00:19:16,440 --> 00:19:19,719
Yeah, your owl called
Owl is with us!

276
00:19:19,720 --> 00:19:21,279
Yeah, he's with us. So what?

277
00:19:21,280 --> 00:19:24,119
He is? Oh! What a relief!

278
00:19:24,120 --> 00:19:27,719
Are you his... 'friends', then?
Yeah, his 'friends'.

279
00:19:27,720 --> 00:19:30,799
- Yes, we are!
- Watch out! Huh!

Huh?

280
00:19:30,800 --> 00:19:32,519
What?

281
00:19:32,520 --> 00:19:35,000
Can you take us to him?

282
00:19:38,120 --> 00:19:41,079
Slow down! Oh, my hat! Wha! Wha!

283
00:19:41,080 --> 00:19:44,959
Hold on to me!
Stop! Stop!

284
00:19:46,800 --> 00:19:49,159
A-A-A-Ah!

285
00:19:49,160 --> 00:19:51,439
Ooh!
Aw, I've got an oar in my...

286
00:19:51,440 --> 00:19:53,800
A-A-A-Ah!
Hold on!

287
00:19:54,880 --> 00:19:57,279
A-A-A-Ah!
Aye!

288
00:19:57,280 --> 00:19:59,319
You know what we should do?

289
00:19:59,320 --> 00:20:01,559
Zig-zag!
Zig-zag, mate!

290
00:20:01,560 --> 00:20:04,119
Wa-a-a-ah!

291
00:20:04,120 --> 00:20:06,559
Woa-oa-oa-oah!

292
00:20:06,560 --> 00:20:09,119
Ho-o-o-o!

293
00:20:09,120 --> 00:20:11,559
A-A-A-Ah!

294
00:20:13,840 --> 00:20:16,519
Phew, what a morning!

295
00:20:16,520 --> 00:20:18,559
Gives me the hot flushes!

296
00:20:18,560 --> 00:20:20,839
I hope they will be back soon.

297
00:20:20,840 --> 00:20:23,040
Aah! Me swag bag!

298
00:20:24,680 --> 00:20:26,959
Ooh! Jack! Come back!

299
00:20:26,960 --> 00:20:30,119
We have to stop the water.
Or it will flood the forest.

300
00:20:30,120 --> 00:20:32,160
I'll fix that!

301
00:20:36,080 --> 00:20:39,439
See? I am an excellent fixer.

302
00:20:39,440 --> 00:20:41,919
Uh... Tusk...

303
00:20:41,920 --> 00:20:44,479
Ooh! Maybe not.
Oh!

304
00:20:44,480 --> 00:20:48,239
Our houses!
We have to check if they're OK!

305
00:20:48,240 --> 00:20:51,119
We have to hurry.
We need to build a dyke.

306
00:20:51,120 --> 00:20:53,519
Now.
A dyke?! A what?

307
00:20:53,520 --> 00:20:56,759
A wall of dirt
that will keep the water out.

308
00:20:56,760 --> 00:20:59,839
Fortunately, I've just picked up
a bunch of shovels dirt cheap.

309
00:20:59,840 --> 00:21:02,199
You can have 'em
at a nice little discount.

310
00:21:02,200 --> 00:21:05,720
Ooh!
I am an EXCELLENT shoveller.

311
00:21:13,720 --> 00:21:15,919
No water here.

312
00:21:15,920 --> 00:21:19,080
Jack? Jack?!

313
00:21:20,040 --> 00:21:21,879
Oh, no.

314
00:21:21,880 --> 00:21:24,119
Hare's stuff will get all wet.

315
00:21:24,120 --> 00:21:25,639
She won't like that...

316
00:21:25,640 --> 00:21:29,119
Get in there.
Good thinking, Jack!

317
00:21:29,120 --> 00:21:32,360
Put everything on the table,
so it won't get wet.

318
00:21:41,560 --> 00:21:44,880
Jellyfish and shark teeth!
Me merchandise!

319
00:21:46,920 --> 00:21:49,719
Our houses! They're flooding!

320
00:21:59,920 --> 00:22:02,440
OK, water...

321
00:22:04,440 --> 00:22:07,480
...this forest isn't big enough
for the both of us!

322
00:22:15,240 --> 00:22:18,120
A-a-a-ah...

323
00:22:25,360 --> 00:22:27,399
Slow down!

324
00:22:27,400 --> 00:22:29,479
Ah, oh, my hat!

325
00:22:29,480 --> 00:22:32,519
Ah! Wha...?! Ah! Ah! A-A-A-Ah!

326
00:22:32,520 --> 00:22:35,120
Wa-a-a-ah!

327
00:22:36,680 --> 00:22:40,439
Welcome... to... The Lodge.

328
00:22:40,440 --> 00:22:42,559
The Lodge...

329
00:22:42,560 --> 00:22:46,439
- Huh?
- The Lodge?
What lodge?

330
00:22:49,000 --> 00:22:51,999
"What lodge?"Let's go in,
- - shall we?
- Yeah!
- Go in?

331
00:22:52,000 --> 00:22:54,039
Where's the door?

332
00:22:56,000 --> 00:22:59,400
"Where's the door?" he says.
Put these on!

333
00:23:01,240 --> 00:23:03,640
What?

334
00:23:25,280 --> 00:23:27,239
Where are we?

335
00:23:31,720 --> 00:23:34,159
Fox! Hare!

336
00:23:34,160 --> 00:23:37,479
A-a-a-ah!
Owl! Oh... oh...

337
00:23:37,480 --> 00:23:40,639
Aw, that's cute.
Don't cry.

338
00:23:40,640 --> 00:23:42,639
What happened to you, Owl?

339
00:23:42,640 --> 00:23:44,679
I ran through the forest,
and, suddenly,

340
00:23:44,680 --> 00:23:46,639
there was all this water and...

341
00:23:46,640 --> 00:23:49,679
oh, Hoohoo!
Have you seen Hoohoo?

342
00:23:49,680 --> 00:23:51,879
Hoohoo is safe at home.

343
00:23:51,880 --> 00:23:54,199
What is all this?

344
00:23:54,200 --> 00:23:56,719
A very watery place.

345
00:23:56,720 --> 00:23:59,000
Owned by...
Me-e-e-e!

346
00:24:01,120 --> 00:24:03,120
Yeah!

347
00:24:07,200 --> 00:24:09,200
Ha-a-a-a!

348
00:24:14,360 --> 00:24:17,160
Ah, ah, ah

349
00:24:18,840 --> 00:24:22,000
♪ Ah, ah, ah...
Ooh!

350
00:24:23,400 --> 00:24:26,759
♪ The Beaver! The Beaver!...

351
00:24:26,760 --> 00:24:29,159
Wow!
♪ The beaver, beaver

352
00:24:29,160 --> 00:24:31,759
♪ Welcome, furry friends,
to my palace of glee

353
00:24:31,760 --> 00:24:35,239
♪ There's a hundred
different toys courtesy of me

354
00:24:35,240 --> 00:24:37,719
♪ Lovingly chiselled
with my two front teeth

355
00:24:37,720 --> 00:24:41,399
♪ I've got gadgets you can play with
That you wouldn't believe

356
00:24:41,400 --> 00:24:44,079
♪ So if you're thinking
that you really ought to go home

357
00:24:44,080 --> 00:24:47,479
♪ Worried that your friends
are feeling slightly alone

358
00:24:47,480 --> 00:24:50,239
♪ Think about the fun
That you could have here with me

359
00:24:50,240 --> 00:24:53,759
♪ If you go back to the forest
Then, you're out of your tree...

360
00:25:00,640 --> 00:25:02,679
Do you like what I've done
- with the place?
- Wow!

361
00:25:02,680 --> 00:25:05,519
The stairs do the walking for us!

362
00:25:05,520 --> 00:25:07,799
What a fantastic home!

363
00:25:07,800 --> 00:25:10,959
Hm,
it's more a playground than a home.

364
00:25:10,960 --> 00:25:14,399
Woo-hoo-hoo!
What's all this great stuff?

365
00:25:14,400 --> 00:25:16,279
Three guesses who made it all?

366
00:25:16,280 --> 00:25:17,999
♪ The beaver!...
That's me!

367
00:25:18,000 --> 00:25:19,679
♪ The beaver!...
Still me!

368
00:25:19,680 --> 00:25:22,999
♪ The beaver! Beaver!...
They're singing about me.

369
00:25:23,000 --> 00:25:25,079
I'm not only a great inventor.

370
00:25:25,080 --> 00:25:27,559
I'm a gifted artist, too.
Do you like it?

371
00:25:27,560 --> 00:25:31,119
I call it "Misunderstood."
Call me Justin, by the way!

372
00:25:31,120 --> 00:25:33,199
Wow! Is this for playing with?

373
00:25:33,200 --> 00:25:35,119
Wha!
It sure is.

374
00:25:35,120 --> 00:25:37,519
Everything you see is
yours for the taking!

375
00:25:37,520 --> 00:25:41,439
Imagine that. I do my best to be
the world's most hospitable host!

376
00:25:41,440 --> 00:25:44,879
In fact, I'm welcoming you
all with open arms! Because I'm...

377
00:25:44,880 --> 00:25:48,599
♪ The Beaver!
Do you believer

378
00:25:48,600 --> 00:25:51,639
♪ In the Beaver, Believer?

379
00:25:51,640 --> 00:25:54,239
♪ So, my furry friends,
you really must forgive me

380
00:25:54,240 --> 00:25:57,439
♪ If my made my points
Somewhat over dramatically

381
00:25:57,440 --> 00:25:59,839
♪ I sense a little hesitance,
and that worries me

382
00:25:59,840 --> 00:26:03,639
♪ Don't be nervous,
I'm as friendly as a beaver can be

383
00:26:03,640 --> 00:26:06,559
♪ Imagine the adventures
You can have if you stay.

384
00:26:06,560 --> 00:26:09,399
♪ How you will never have
to work again, just play every day

385
00:26:09,400 --> 00:26:12,519
♪ Because life in Beaver Lodge
is just the best it can be

386
00:26:12,520 --> 00:26:14,039
♪ You'll be Beaver Believers

387
00:26:14,040 --> 00:26:20,080
♪ If you stay here forever
with me-e-e-e ♪

388
00:26:23,960 --> 00:26:26,239
Can we please go back home now?

389
00:26:26,240 --> 00:26:29,559
Home?! Why would you wanna go home?

390
00:26:29,560 --> 00:26:31,919
We could have so much fun here.

391
00:26:31,920 --> 00:26:35,679
This is the best home in the world!
Home?

392
00:26:35,680 --> 00:26:39,279
All the gadgets
and games don't make it home.

393
00:26:39,280 --> 00:26:41,919
No? What does, then?

394
00:26:41,920 --> 00:26:44,079
Well... uh...

395
00:26:44,080 --> 00:26:47,239
a really beautiful homemade cake.

396
00:26:47,240 --> 00:26:49,519
Hm.

397
00:26:49,520 --> 00:26:51,959
- Oh?
- Oh.
- Ooh.

398
00:26:51,960 --> 00:26:54,759
Wow!

399
00:26:54,760 --> 00:26:58,079
That is the most fantastic cake
I've ever seen!

400
00:26:58,080 --> 00:27:01,639
Well... uh...

401
00:27:01,640 --> 00:27:04,479
Look, it's me!
But... But...

402
00:27:04,480 --> 00:27:08,599
But... But Hoohoo and our friends
will be wondering where we are!

403
00:27:08,600 --> 00:27:10,959
Ah, no problem!

404
00:27:10,960 --> 00:27:14,759
I will send the Rats
to invite them, too! Rats!

405
00:27:14,760 --> 00:27:16,639
But...
Pi-rats!

406
00:27:16,640 --> 00:27:18,879
Pi-rats!
You've told him!

407
00:27:18,880 --> 00:27:22,319
Yes, yes, whatever.
Go and get the 'friends', will you?

408
00:27:22,320 --> 00:27:24,919
- Yeah!
- To the boat!
To the boat!

409
00:27:27,400 --> 00:27:29,799
Wha! Whoo! Wey!

410
00:27:29,800 --> 00:27:32,319
Hey! Watch it, will you. Woah!

411
00:27:32,320 --> 00:27:34,839
I'll squirt you with this water gun!
You put that down!

412
00:27:34,840 --> 00:27:37,279
I'm not putting it down!
That is my water gun!

413
00:27:37,280 --> 00:27:40,879
Give me that back!
- Give it here, you!
- Stop it!

414
00:27:40,880 --> 00:27:42,799
Let it go.
Let the handle go.

415
00:27:44,960 --> 00:27:47,160
No, leave it alone!

416
00:27:48,320 --> 00:27:51,680
Look out!

417
00:27:57,720 --> 00:28:00,319
- What?! My dyke!
- Oh!

418
00:28:00,320 --> 00:28:03,919
- Now look what you've done!
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- Are you really pirates?

419
00:28:03,920 --> 00:28:05,559
Pi-RATS!

420
00:28:05,560 --> 00:28:08,239
That's nice.
Out of my way!

421
00:28:11,800 --> 00:28:13,839
Help!

422
00:28:13,840 --> 00:28:16,639
You are really strong, prickly pig!

423
00:28:16,640 --> 00:28:19,519
Very, very strong.
I know.

424
00:28:19,520 --> 00:28:21,399
Anyway, we've come to tell you...

425
00:28:21,400 --> 00:28:23,999
We've come to tell you
that your friends found Owl.

426
00:28:24,000 --> 00:28:27,279
Oh! Thank all the ice
of the South Pole! Where are they?

427
00:28:27,280 --> 00:28:29,879
They... are in the Lodge.

428
00:28:29,880 --> 00:28:32,199
In the Lo-o-o-odge.
Yeah, in the Lodge, alright.

429
00:28:32,200 --> 00:28:34,399
Yeah, you're all invited!
Yeah, you're all invited!

430
00:28:34,400 --> 00:28:36,799
We can give you a lift!
In our pi-rat speedboat.

431
00:28:36,800 --> 00:28:39,679
In our pi-rat speedboat.
It's lovely. It's got two engines.

432
00:28:39,680 --> 00:28:42,399
Yeah, and a wheel.
No way!

433
00:28:42,400 --> 00:28:45,439
Come on, Jack! Pirates love water!

434
00:28:45,440 --> 00:28:48,639
I'm not a pirate. I'm a thief.

435
00:28:48,640 --> 00:28:50,679
Uh... Sorry, guys.

436
00:28:50,680 --> 00:28:53,279
Uh... Bit busy here.
Maybe some other time.

437
00:28:53,280 --> 00:28:56,399
Right, what about you, then, Prickly
- Pig?
- Yeah, what about you, eh?

438
00:28:56,400 --> 00:29:00,319
Can't. Have to save the forest.

439
00:29:00,320 --> 00:29:03,719
By moving dirt?
Shifting dirt about?

440
00:29:03,720 --> 00:29:06,799
By building a dyke. All alone.

441
00:29:06,800 --> 00:29:10,439
A dyke?
"A dyke," he says.

442
00:29:10,440 --> 00:29:13,399
That ain't no dyke, mate,
my muscled friend!

443
00:29:13,400 --> 00:29:15,479
Good muscles, though.
Yeah, good muscles.

444
00:29:15,480 --> 00:29:18,839
My dyke is exactly
the way it should be.

445
00:29:18,840 --> 00:29:22,079
Yeah, but isn't a dyke...
- ...Meant to stop the water?
- Yes.

446
00:29:22,080 --> 00:29:26,079
- Stop the water.
- Well... yes,
but it... it isn't finished yet!

447
00:29:26,080 --> 00:29:28,359
Well, we can help.
Yeah, we can help!

448
00:29:28,360 --> 00:29:30,959
Yeah, we can help. We know all
about dykes and dams, don't we?

449
00:29:30,960 --> 00:29:33,279
Yeah! All about them.
Yeah! All about building them.

450
00:29:33,280 --> 00:29:35,839
Right, just give me some of
- that sand here.
- That...

451
00:29:35,840 --> 00:29:39,079
That's... Stick that in that hole.
- Yeah, that looks good.
- Looks good.

452
00:29:39,080 --> 00:29:42,119
No, thank you.
Anyone could make that.

453
00:29:42,120 --> 00:29:44,239
I am building something...

454
00:29:44,240 --> 00:29:46,279
different.

455
00:29:46,280 --> 00:29:49,839
Different?! Different is not going
to stop the water, Prickly Pig.

456
00:29:49,840 --> 00:29:51,959
No, it's not going
to stop the water.

457
00:29:51,960 --> 00:29:55,479
But your muscles,
together with our brains, will!

458
00:29:55,480 --> 00:29:58,079
Yeah! Our brains, yeah!
Ah, no, thanks.

459
00:29:58,080 --> 00:30:01,199
My muscles know everything
- they need to know!
- Come on.

460
00:30:01,200 --> 00:30:03,599
Together, we'll build
that dyke in no time!

461
00:30:03,600 --> 00:30:06,039
Yeah! No time at all!
And then, you can come with us!

462
00:30:06,040 --> 00:30:08,359
Yeah, you can come with us.
It's great where we're going.

463
00:30:08,360 --> 00:30:10,839
Come on, we'll make a great team!
Yeah! Great team!

464
00:30:10,840 --> 00:30:14,479
No! I don't want help,
and I don't like teams!

465
00:30:14,480 --> 00:30:17,759
I am an EXCELLENT shoveller,
and I can do it all alone!

466
00:30:17,760 --> 00:30:20,879
OK, prickly pig.
OK, have it your way.

467
00:30:20,880 --> 00:30:24,239
Let us know if you wanna change
- your mind.
- Yeah, let us know.

468
00:30:24,240 --> 00:30:26,319
Yeah. Hey! Where is me water gun?

469
00:30:26,320 --> 00:30:28,199
YOUR water gun?
Where is my water gun?

470
00:30:28,200 --> 00:30:30,679
It's not your water gun.
- It's my water gun!
- Bye now!

471
00:30:30,680 --> 00:30:32,839
Don't be strangers!

472
00:30:32,840 --> 00:30:35,200
Stupid rats.

473
00:30:38,240 --> 00:30:40,319
While we wait for your friends,

474
00:30:40,320 --> 00:30:43,680
let me show you the high point
of this lodge. Follow me!

475
00:30:45,120 --> 00:30:47,879
Watch this.

476
00:30:47,880 --> 00:30:50,719
O-O-O-Oh!

477
00:30:56,080 --> 00:30:59,400
Woo-hoo-hoo!

478
00:31:03,040 --> 00:31:05,719
Look!

479
00:31:05,720 --> 00:31:08,159
Oh.
So cool!

480
00:31:08,160 --> 00:31:11,240
I know. I know.
It is a lot to take in.

481
00:31:12,600 --> 00:31:14,600
So much water...

482
00:31:15,400 --> 00:31:17,359
Isn't it marvellous?

483
00:31:17,360 --> 00:31:20,039
You can almost see home.

484
00:31:20,040 --> 00:31:22,600
You can?
Binoculars?

485
00:31:26,480 --> 00:31:29,159
The forest! It's flooding!

486
00:31:29,160 --> 00:31:31,679
Hoo-hoo, no-o-o-o!

487
00:31:31,680 --> 00:31:34,559
Come, come, don't exaggerate.

488
00:31:34,560 --> 00:31:37,279
But our homes! Our friends!

489
00:31:37,280 --> 00:31:40,160
And Hoohoo!
Let me see!

490
00:31:41,280 --> 00:31:43,799
It doesn't look that bad.

491
00:31:43,800 --> 00:31:46,559
Please, let's focus
on the positives.

492
00:31:46,560 --> 00:31:48,439
Like MY work here.

493
00:31:48,440 --> 00:31:50,959
A wonderful lodge, a great lake,

494
00:31:50,960 --> 00:31:53,399
and you haven't even seen-
But the forest!

495
00:31:53,400 --> 00:31:55,199
...Will be fine.

496
00:31:55,200 --> 00:31:58,599
And besides, you could always come
and live with me!

497
00:31:58,600 --> 00:32:00,679
Could we?

498
00:32:00,680 --> 00:32:02,439
Of course.

499
00:32:02,440 --> 00:32:05,159
My generosity is without limits.

500
00:32:05,160 --> 00:32:08,719
No, we can't!
We need to go home!

501
00:32:08,720 --> 00:32:12,279
Oh, come on, Hare.
This is the greatest place ever!

502
00:32:12,280 --> 00:32:15,479
There is so much fun stuff
we haven't even tried yet.

503
00:32:15,480 --> 00:32:17,919
Bring us down! Now!

504
00:32:17,920 --> 00:32:20,559
As you wish.

505
00:32:25,720 --> 00:32:27,720
Are you coming, Fox?

506
00:32:28,560 --> 00:32:30,119
Um...

507
00:32:32,920 --> 00:32:35,639
Come sit and relax a bit
before we go back down again.

508
00:32:35,640 --> 00:32:37,679
You haven't seen anything yet, Fox.

509
00:32:37,680 --> 00:32:40,479
Wait till you see my obstacle course

510
00:32:40,480 --> 00:32:42,159
and my parachute cannon

511
00:32:42,160 --> 00:32:45,479
and my jumping waterfalls
and my delicious...

512
00:32:45,480 --> 00:32:47,760
...sorbet.

513
00:32:49,240 --> 00:32:53,399
Um... Yeah, I think I'll stay
for just a little bit longer.

514
00:32:53,400 --> 00:32:56,399
Fox?!
Please come with us, Fox.

515
00:32:56,400 --> 00:32:59,359
Try this.
One of my many delicious recipes.

516
00:32:59,360 --> 00:33:01,399
Ooh!

517
00:33:06,600 --> 00:33:09,039
Do we have to?
Yes.

518
00:33:09,040 --> 00:33:11,719
Unless you want to stay here, too.

519
00:33:14,760 --> 00:33:17,719
I can fly. I can fly.

520
00:33:17,720 --> 00:33:20,640
It's all going to be fine...
because I can fly!

521
00:33:21,640 --> 00:33:24,719
Ungrateful lot. Just you wait.

522
00:33:24,720 --> 00:33:28,399
I'll make this place
so, so, so much fun,

523
00:33:28,400 --> 00:33:30,599
no one will ever wanna leave again.

524
00:33:30,600 --> 00:33:32,639
Ooh...

525
00:33:32,640 --> 00:33:34,680
maybe that was
one sorbet too many.

526
00:33:35,520 --> 00:33:39,280
You made the right choice, dear Fox.

527
00:33:40,400 --> 00:33:43,919
Oh, great! What shall we do now?

528
00:33:43,920 --> 00:33:45,959
Want to see my masterpiece...

529
00:33:45,960 --> 00:33:47,879
up close?

530
00:33:47,880 --> 00:33:50,880
Ho-o-o-o... masterpiece?

531
00:34:20,200 --> 00:34:23,959
So... oh, this... this is it, is it?
This is... This is your masterpiece?

532
00:34:23,960 --> 00:34:26,000
Extraordinary, isn't it?

533
00:34:26,920 --> 00:34:29,919
The water of the creek
can't flow away because of the dam.

534
00:34:29,920 --> 00:34:34,159
And that is what created
- this glorious lake.
- Oh.

535
00:34:34,160 --> 00:34:37,759
OK. Uh...
Never mind.

536
00:34:37,760 --> 00:34:41,400
After all, we cannot
all be geniuses, now, can we?

537
00:34:42,400 --> 00:34:44,759
Um... Shall we go
and play in the Lodge?

538
00:34:44,760 --> 00:34:46,639
PLAY?! No, no, no...

539
00:34:46,640 --> 00:34:50,079
I am going to do
some more great inventing.

540
00:34:50,080 --> 00:34:52,439
You... You go and enjoy yourself.

541
00:34:54,520 --> 00:34:56,799
Whee-ee-ee-ee!

542
00:34:56,800 --> 00:35:00,279
Yeah! Whoo-oo-oo-oo!

543
00:35:00,280 --> 00:35:03,839
Oh, wow! This is grea-ea-ea-eat!

544
00:35:03,840 --> 00:35:07,519
Woo-hoo-hoo! Whee-ee-ee-ee!

545
00:35:09,840 --> 00:35:13,440
Wow! Again! Again!

546
00:35:17,680 --> 00:35:19,840
Wow!

547
00:35:20,920 --> 00:35:23,599
Whoa-oa-oa-oah!

548
00:35:31,640 --> 00:35:34,439
Oh! Oh! OH! Woah-oh-hoh!

549
00:35:36,400 --> 00:35:39,879
Oh.

550
00:35:39,880 --> 00:35:42,360
Oh... not again.

551
00:35:45,000 --> 00:35:47,000
Hey...

552
00:35:53,120 --> 00:35:55,359
OK!

553
00:35:57,480 --> 00:36:01,199
Beaver! Look! I made something, too!

554
00:36:01,200 --> 00:36:04,319
Huh? What's that?!

555
00:36:04,320 --> 00:36:06,599
Don't tell me my machine did that?!

556
00:36:06,600 --> 00:36:09,960
Hm, I'll fix it later.

557
00:36:24,000 --> 00:36:26,119
Owl! Hare!

558
00:36:26,120 --> 00:36:28,760
Hoohoo!
Where were ya?

559
00:36:29,600 --> 00:36:31,960
Are you all OK?
What about our houses?

560
00:36:35,440 --> 00:36:38,879
Oh, no! My den!
Fox is not coming.

561
00:36:56,360 --> 00:36:58,319
Oh, no!

562
00:37:05,760 --> 00:37:07,680
Oh, no...

563
00:37:10,000 --> 00:37:13,000
Here, take this.

564
00:37:15,600 --> 00:37:17,600
Careful now.
Thank you, dear.

565
00:37:24,720 --> 00:37:27,199
You push up hill.
You push up hill.

566
00:37:35,280 --> 00:37:37,279
She is a bit sad, Hoohoo.

567
00:37:37,280 --> 00:37:39,319
But she will be fine.

568
00:37:51,080 --> 00:37:53,120
What shall we do now?

569
00:37:56,720 --> 00:38:00,319
Oh. This isn't fun at all!

570
00:38:04,400 --> 00:38:06,400
Oh!

571
00:38:07,440 --> 00:38:10,639
What's all this?

572
00:38:19,880 --> 00:38:22,480
Ha-ha, Beaver! Beaver!

573
00:38:24,720 --> 00:38:27,159
Oh!

574
00:38:31,720 --> 00:38:35,000
Oh! That is so amazing!

575
00:38:38,760 --> 00:38:41,999
Whoo! That is so-o-o-o amazing!

576
00:38:43,440 --> 00:38:46,359
Mermaid! Mermaid! I'm here!

577
00:38:46,360 --> 00:38:48,160
Look, it's Fox!

578
00:38:50,320 --> 00:38:52,320
Our forest!

579
00:38:54,040 --> 00:38:56,719
Oh, no!

580
00:38:56,720 --> 00:38:59,199
Hare!

581
00:38:59,200 --> 00:39:02,159
What are you doing here?
This room is off limits, my friend.

582
00:39:02,160 --> 00:39:04,239
No guests allowed.

583
00:39:04,240 --> 00:39:06,399
Our forest is completely flooded.

584
00:39:06,400 --> 00:39:09,039
Well, obviously.

585
00:39:09,040 --> 00:39:12,159
But you said it would be fine!
Well, it is fine.

586
00:39:12,160 --> 00:39:15,119
I see a great lake
and a wonderful lodge.

587
00:39:15,120 --> 00:39:17,599
I see a genius Beaver who offers

588
00:39:17,600 --> 00:39:20,759
to share
his tremendous glory with you.

589
00:39:20,760 --> 00:39:24,159
If all of that is not fine,
I don't know what is.

590
00:39:24,160 --> 00:39:27,119
But what about our forest?
What about the den?

591
00:39:27,120 --> 00:39:29,839
Our den is
the most important thing to Hare.

592
00:39:29,840 --> 00:39:33,119
The flooding is caused by the Dam!

593
00:39:33,120 --> 00:39:36,519
You need to it take down.
- Immediately!
- Take it down?!

594
00:39:36,520 --> 00:39:39,399
Yes! So the water can flow away

595
00:39:39,400 --> 00:39:42,159
and the lake will go down!
Then, we can save the forest.

596
00:39:42,160 --> 00:39:45,879
You want ME
to take down my life's work?

597
00:39:45,880 --> 00:39:48,879
So everything that
I have built will be destroyed?

598
00:39:48,880 --> 00:39:52,359
But you destroyed our forest!
Silence.

599
00:39:52,360 --> 00:39:54,560
This is non-negotiable.

600
00:39:55,760 --> 00:39:58,800
I want to go to Hare.
I want to go back to the forest.

601
00:39:59,880 --> 00:40:03,679
You decided to stay here.
I need to go and see my friends!

602
00:40:03,680 --> 00:40:06,519
Your friends?
Well.. what about your friends?!

603
00:40:06,520 --> 00:40:08,999
What... What good are your friends?!

604
00:40:09,000 --> 00:40:11,039
I thought I was your friend!

605
00:40:11,040 --> 00:40:14,479
I have everything to offer!
They have literally nothing!

606
00:40:14,480 --> 00:40:17,239
Everything they have is under water!

607
00:40:24,360 --> 00:40:26,559
The water won't hurt us, Hoohoo.

608
00:40:26,560 --> 00:40:28,600
We are perfectly safe.

609
00:40:29,840 --> 00:40:32,880
I can fly. I can fly.

610
00:40:34,720 --> 00:40:37,040
Perhaps we can just stay here.

611
00:40:38,920 --> 00:40:42,239
I wanted
to save the forest!

612
00:40:42,240 --> 00:40:45,079
But I couldn't.
I wasn't good enough.

613
00:40:47,400 --> 00:40:49,439
I tried my best.

614
00:40:49,440 --> 00:40:52,119
And I am such a good digger,
but I couldn't dig enough,

615
00:40:52,120 --> 00:40:54,760
and now, everything is under water!

616
00:40:57,080 --> 00:40:59,439
Oh, we'll be fine...

617
00:40:59,440 --> 00:41:01,320
won't we, Hare?

618
00:41:02,400 --> 00:41:04,400
We could make it work.

619
00:41:08,840 --> 00:41:10,919
We can't stay here.

620
00:41:10,920 --> 00:41:12,959
But we ain't got no boat.

621
00:41:14,960 --> 00:41:17,760
We are stuck up here forever.

622
00:41:20,760 --> 00:41:24,960
Oh, Fox... I could really use
one of your crazy ideas now.

623
00:41:26,680 --> 00:41:28,920
What would you do?

624
00:41:30,320 --> 00:41:33,199
OK. Uh... You're right.
Uh... Y-You are my friend.

625
00:41:33,200 --> 00:41:36,079
So, um... shall we play a game?

626
00:41:36,080 --> 00:41:39,119
Why?
Because that's what friends do.

627
00:41:39,120 --> 00:41:41,479
They do?

628
00:41:41,480 --> 00:41:44,919
Well... what do you want to play?
Swim? Waterpolo?

629
00:41:44,920 --> 00:41:48,119
Jetski?
Um... Hide and seek!

630
00:41:48,120 --> 00:41:51,119
What?! That isn't even a water game.

631
00:41:51,120 --> 00:41:54,079
You hide, and I seek! I bet...

632
00:41:54,080 --> 00:41:56,159
you're really good at hide and seek.

633
00:41:56,160 --> 00:41:58,359
Well... you know...

634
00:41:58,360 --> 00:42:00,759
I mean, this place is massive,
and it's yours,

635
00:42:00,760 --> 00:42:03,359
and you know everything.
Oh, please.

636
00:42:03,360 --> 00:42:06,199
And it will be really difficult
for me to find you!

637
00:42:06,200 --> 00:42:09,079
Well... OK, then.

638
00:42:09,080 --> 00:42:10,959
Right.

639
00:42:10,960 --> 00:42:13,119
One, two...

640
00:42:13,120 --> 00:42:16,040
three, four...

641
00:42:23,160 --> 00:42:25,160
I have to destroy that dam!

642
00:42:28,120 --> 00:42:30,399
We may not have a boat...

643
00:42:30,400 --> 00:42:32,559
but we can build one!

644
00:42:32,560 --> 00:42:34,759
I mean, I've got the tools,

645
00:42:34,760 --> 00:42:36,839
but I ain't got any wood.

646
00:42:36,840 --> 00:42:39,439
We have all of this!

647
00:42:39,440 --> 00:42:42,239
Not your stuff!
Uh-huh.

648
00:42:42,240 --> 00:42:44,760
It will get all wet!
It will be ruined!

649
00:42:45,880 --> 00:42:49,119
I know. But it'll be worth it.

650
00:42:53,920 --> 00:42:56,440
Catch!
Got it!

651
00:43:01,360 --> 00:43:03,599
Mm...

652
00:43:07,760 --> 00:43:09,679
OK, then...

653
00:43:13,200 --> 00:43:15,279
Great boat, Hare.

654
00:43:15,280 --> 00:43:17,999
Yes!
Let's go.

655
00:43:18,000 --> 00:43:20,040
This way!

656
00:43:25,280 --> 00:43:27,280
You're the lookout, Hoohoo.

657
00:43:28,120 --> 00:43:31,559
Beaver! Beaver!

658
00:43:31,560 --> 00:43:33,919
Where are you?!

659
00:43:33,920 --> 00:43:36,079
Oh, where could he be?

660
00:43:36,080 --> 00:43:39,199
He is such a good hider,
that beaver.

661
00:43:39,200 --> 00:43:41,960
In fact, the best hider
I think I've ever seen!

662
00:43:57,560 --> 00:43:59,800
Oh! AH!

663
00:44:07,200 --> 00:44:08,799
OK!

664
00:44:12,200 --> 00:44:14,200
Oh!

665
00:44:15,160 --> 00:44:17,680
Oh!

666
00:44:21,040 --> 00:44:23,159
Uh!

667
00:44:26,840 --> 00:44:29,599
Hee!

668
00:44:29,600 --> 00:44:32,599
I don't want a new one!
I want the old one!

669
00:44:32,600 --> 00:44:34,999
- What?
- I said, I-
Da-da-da!

670
00:44:35,000 --> 00:44:38,199
- ...don't want a new one.
- Look, sh!
- - Sh!
- I want an old one.
- No, look!

671
00:44:38,200 --> 00:44:41,240
Look, what? Oh!

672
00:45:00,160 --> 00:45:02,400
Land ahoy!

673
00:45:05,920 --> 00:45:09,079
Oh! Fox!

674
00:45:09,080 --> 00:45:10,759
Huh?

675
00:45:10,760 --> 00:45:13,519
Oh, oh, ooh! Oh, Foxy!
Oh, oh!

676
00:45:13,520 --> 00:45:15,759
Hi, Tusk. I missed you, too.

677
00:45:15,760 --> 00:45:18,600
Ooh!
Hi, Hare!

678
00:45:19,400 --> 00:45:22,640
Hare I... I want
to come home with you.

679
00:45:23,480 --> 00:45:26,719
There is no home anymore.
Yes, I know!

680
00:45:26,720 --> 00:45:29,599
That is why I'm trying
to destroy the dam!

681
00:45:29,600 --> 00:45:33,279
Ooh, let me do it!
I am an EXCELLENT destroyer!

682
00:45:36,280 --> 00:45:38,679
I thought you loved it here.

683
00:45:42,600 --> 00:45:45,159
What are you doing?

684
00:45:45,160 --> 00:45:47,320
You want to destroy my dam!

685
00:45:48,960 --> 00:45:51,559
I invited you into my lodge.

686
00:45:51,560 --> 00:45:53,639
I shared my greatness.

687
00:45:53,640 --> 00:45:56,359
I even played
that stupid game with you.

688
00:45:56,360 --> 00:45:59,479
And this is how you THANK me?
But...

689
00:45:59,480 --> 00:46:02,359
Did you really think
you could take on this genius

690
00:46:02,360 --> 00:46:04,119
and DESTROY MY MASTERPIECE?

691
00:46:04,120 --> 00:46:06,959
But we have to safe the forest!

692
00:46:06,960 --> 00:46:09,799
Oh. But there are so many forests.

693
00:46:09,800 --> 00:46:13,200
And a genius dam like this?
THERE'S ONLY ONE!

694
00:46:14,120 --> 00:46:17,039
This is what happens
when you mess with the Beaver.

695
00:46:23,040 --> 00:46:26,519
I am very, very disappointed.

696
00:46:36,640 --> 00:46:40,319
Aye, prickly pig,
that'll never work.

697
00:46:40,320 --> 00:46:42,360
That's never gonna work.
No way!

698
00:46:43,400 --> 00:46:45,560
Ooh!

699
00:46:53,120 --> 00:46:54,999
Look at that!

700
00:46:55,000 --> 00:46:57,039
Ooh! You're welcome.

701
00:46:57,040 --> 00:47:00,199
Yeah, you're welcome.
Stupid rats.

702
00:47:00,200 --> 00:47:04,039
But we don't have to stay here
forever, do we, Hare?

703
00:47:04,040 --> 00:47:06,999
That would be very bad for business.

704
00:47:07,000 --> 00:47:09,679
I can't live in a box!

705
00:47:09,680 --> 00:47:11,800
Not even a big box.

706
00:47:13,200 --> 00:47:14,959
I am sorry.

707
00:47:14,960 --> 00:47:17,000
So now you're sorry.

708
00:47:17,880 --> 00:47:20,680
But...
Leave... me... alone!

709
00:47:22,760 --> 00:47:24,759
...at least, we're together.

710
00:47:24,760 --> 00:47:27,319
I miss my tree.

711
00:47:27,320 --> 00:47:29,360
I miss my mud.

712
00:47:30,320 --> 00:47:32,560
I miss my mermaid.

713
00:47:37,040 --> 00:47:39,080
Owl?

714
00:47:42,440 --> 00:47:44,919
Owl?

715
00:47:44,920 --> 00:47:48,320
Seal? Fox?

716
00:47:49,840 --> 00:47:53,920
Hare? Where is everyone?!

717
00:47:57,560 --> 00:47:59,959
Oh, come on. guys! Cheer up!

718
00:47:59,960 --> 00:48:03,919
There are still so many good things.
Like what?

719
00:48:03,920 --> 00:48:05,959
Well...

720
00:48:05,960 --> 00:48:08,599
like the memories of all
the good times that we shared...

721
00:48:08,600 --> 00:48:10,639
all the laughs that we had...

722
00:48:10,640 --> 00:48:12,680
How can that help us now?

723
00:48:13,520 --> 00:48:17,039
Well... remember
when we all gave you Hoohoo

724
00:48:17,040 --> 00:48:19,079
as a birthday present?

725
00:48:19,080 --> 00:48:22,559
That was one of the best days ever!

726
00:48:22,560 --> 00:48:26,479
And when YOU won
the Yearly Forest Sport Competition.

727
00:48:26,480 --> 00:48:30,679
Well...
...I am an EXCELLENT sporter.

728
00:48:30,680 --> 00:48:32,959
You are! And Ping Wing,

729
00:48:32,960 --> 00:48:35,279
remember when you had
a sunstroke and-

730
00:48:35,280 --> 00:48:38,159
you brought me
ice creams to cool me down!

731
00:48:38,160 --> 00:48:40,999
And I made you
a drawing of an iceberg!

732
00:48:44,880 --> 00:48:47,999
♪ I can't be blue
When I'm stuck here with you

733
00:48:48,000 --> 00:48:50,039
♪ No, I can't...
It's true!

734
00:48:50,040 --> 00:48:52,759
It's impossible to do

735
00:48:52,760 --> 00:48:55,599
♪ I'm in a lake
But I'm thinking of cake

736
00:48:55,600 --> 00:48:58,119
♪ Made by you...
Oh, yeah?

737
00:48:58,120 --> 00:49:00,359
You said Beaver's cake was the best.

738
00:49:00,360 --> 00:49:03,119
I was wrong!
It wasn't the best...

739
00:49:03,120 --> 00:49:05,919
because it wasn't made by you!

740
00:49:05,920 --> 00:49:09,319
♪ It doesn't matter much
If we're stuck in a jail

741
00:49:09,320 --> 00:49:13,239
♪ We can imagine
we're escaping in a boat with a sail

742
00:49:13,240 --> 00:49:17,119
♪ Whenever you feel sad
Cos things are desperately wrong

743
00:49:17,120 --> 00:49:20,759
♪ Remember, we've all got each other
And together, we are strong!...

744
00:49:20,760 --> 00:49:24,559
I am very strong, am I not?
You are!

745
00:49:24,560 --> 00:49:27,600
♪ I've got you
And you've got me...

746
00:49:31,920 --> 00:49:35,359
♪ Friends who love you
Set you free!

747
00:49:35,360 --> 00:49:39,279
♪ What is it with this song?
We just have to sing along!

748
00:49:39,280 --> 00:49:42,160
♪ There's no point feeling sorry

749
00:49:43,040 --> 00:49:45,000
♪ For the mess we're in

750
00:49:46,440 --> 00:49:48,840
♪ As long as you've got laughter

751
00:49:49,720 --> 00:49:53,279
♪ Your life is a Win-win-win!...
What on Earth...!

752
00:49:53,280 --> 00:49:55,639
Let's take it up a notch, Tusk!

753
00:49:55,640 --> 00:49:59,079
Oh! Ja!
-Yeah, go on, Prickly Pig!
- Yeah!

754
00:49:59,080 --> 00:50:02,319
♪ Don't you know
That we will always be together

755
00:50:02,320 --> 00:50:05,320
♪ I will never ever leave you again!

756
00:50:06,160 --> 00:50:08,879
♪ We are gonna be together forever

757
00:50:08,880 --> 00:50:11,999
♪ We are gonna be together
Till the end...

758
00:50:12,000 --> 00:50:15,159
# We are friends

759
00:50:15,160 --> 00:50:18,279
♪ We are friends...

760
00:50:18,280 --> 00:50:20,479
Wait a sec, what am I doing?
Why are they singing?

761
00:50:20,480 --> 00:50:23,319
Why are they so happy? And...
And where did they find a drum-kit?

762
00:50:23,320 --> 00:50:24,919
Rats!

763
00:50:24,920 --> 00:50:28,560
Please come
to the control room. NOW.

764
00:50:29,400 --> 00:50:32,000
♪ We are friends

765
00:50:32,920 --> 00:50:35,919
♪ We are friends

766
00:50:35,920 --> 00:50:39,240
♪ We are frie-e-e-ends ♪

767
00:50:40,800 --> 00:50:42,719
Why are you singing
with the prisoners?

768
00:50:42,720 --> 00:50:45,319
Well... uh... you know...
They're not so bad.

769
00:50:45,320 --> 00:50:47,479
No, not so bad, are they, really.

770
00:50:47,480 --> 00:50:49,639
They are disrespectful,

771
00:50:49,640 --> 00:50:52,879
and have the nerve to
entertain themselves with NOTHING!

772
00:50:52,880 --> 00:50:56,279
Well... they are kind of fun,
really, aren't they?!
Yeah, no, they're good fun.

773
00:50:56,280 --> 00:50:59,079
Quite good fun for prisoners.
- Had a good laugh.
- Keep 'em locked up!

774
00:50:59,080 --> 00:51:01,719
That was very uplifting, Fox.

775
00:51:01,720 --> 00:51:04,039
Yes... But still...

776
00:51:04,040 --> 00:51:06,399
I don't wanna stay here.

777
00:51:06,400 --> 00:51:08,519
I need to see the stars at night!

778
00:51:08,520 --> 00:51:12,039
Me, too. Wanna roll in the dirt.

779
00:51:12,040 --> 00:51:15,680
Why would we leave?
We have no place to go.

780
00:51:16,880 --> 00:51:19,559
We'll find a new place!

781
00:51:19,560 --> 00:51:21,559
And I'll build a new den for you.

782
00:51:21,560 --> 00:51:23,559
Much nicer than our old den.

783
00:51:23,560 --> 00:51:25,959
We just need to stick together.

784
00:51:25,960 --> 00:51:28,000
Huh.

785
00:51:30,840 --> 00:51:34,319
That's it!
It is?

786
00:51:34,320 --> 00:51:36,719
We can dig a tunnel.

787
00:51:36,720 --> 00:51:38,799
All the way to the dam.

788
00:51:38,800 --> 00:51:41,399
And escape on the raft!

789
00:51:41,400 --> 00:51:43,959
Oh, yes! Can I? Can I? Can...?

790
00:51:43,960 --> 00:51:45,999
I am an EXCELLENT digger!

791
00:51:46,000 --> 00:51:48,799
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah...
We have to be careful.

792
00:51:48,800 --> 00:51:52,159
Beaver might be watching us.

793
00:51:52,160 --> 00:51:55,039
I promoted you
from sewer rats

794
00:51:55,040 --> 00:51:57,279
to respectable water rats.

795
00:51:57,280 --> 00:51:59,439
All completely selfless

796
00:51:59,440 --> 00:52:02,879
without asking
for anything in return.

797
00:52:02,880 --> 00:52:05,039
Hang on...
we did help you build that dam.

798
00:52:05,040 --> 00:52:07,799
Yeah, there was the dam. And the
Lodge. I've still got the blisters.

799
00:52:07,800 --> 00:52:10,639
Yeah! He's got the blisters!
I've got the blisters as well.

800
00:52:10,640 --> 00:52:13,119
You should be grateful
for the opportunity

801
00:52:13,120 --> 00:52:16,799
to be part of MY MASTERPIECE.

802
00:52:16,800 --> 00:52:19,599
Oh... here we go.
Delusions of grandeur.

803
00:52:19,600 --> 00:52:22,040
We need to distract Beaver...

804
00:52:22,880 --> 00:52:24,600
I'll do it.

805
00:52:27,000 --> 00:52:29,879
Oh, Owl, are you sure?

806
00:52:29,880 --> 00:52:31,920
Yes, I am.

807
00:52:33,000 --> 00:52:35,639
See you on the other side!

808
00:52:35,640 --> 00:52:37,919
Beaver! Beaver!

809
00:52:37,920 --> 00:52:40,479
Look at me! I am escaping!

810
00:52:40,480 --> 00:52:43,799
That is one brave Owl.
I am escaping!

811
00:52:43,800 --> 00:52:46,159
Now, let's dig!

812
00:52:46,160 --> 00:52:49,839
That's a job for me-e-e-e!

813
00:52:58,400 --> 00:53:00,479
Beaver! Beaver!

814
00:53:00,480 --> 00:53:04,759
Look at me. I am escapi-i-i-ing!

815
00:53:04,760 --> 00:53:08,959
Look at this! Have you ever seen
such an ingenious slide?

816
00:53:08,960 --> 00:53:12,439
And this! Bet you never saw
an indoor waterfall anywhere else.

817
00:53:12,440 --> 00:53:15,719
And here! Enough lemonade
for the rest of your life.

818
00:53:15,720 --> 00:53:17,999
And... And... And the lake I made.

819
00:53:18,000 --> 00:53:20,239
All that water. You like water,

820
00:53:20,240 --> 00:53:24,200
don't you, just like me!
Everybody likes water!

821
00:53:25,520 --> 00:53:28,399
Yeah, water!
Yes show us the water! Yeah!

822
00:53:28,400 --> 00:53:30,759
I'm not scared...

823
00:53:30,760 --> 00:53:33,079
I'm a bird.

824
00:53:33,080 --> 00:53:36,039
I can fly. I can fly.

825
00:53:36,040 --> 00:53:40,160
I can... ooh...
uh... fly-y-y-y!

826
00:53:42,880 --> 00:53:45,519
You see?
Wow.

827
00:53:45,520 --> 00:53:47,919
Yeah, very impressive,
Boss, that, yeah.

828
00:53:47,920 --> 00:53:50,200
Yeah, very impressive that is,
- isn't it?
- Wow!

829
00:53:52,160 --> 00:53:54,600
Owl? Owl?

830
00:53:55,560 --> 00:53:58,199
A-A-A-Ah!
Owl!

831
00:53:58,200 --> 00:54:00,479
I knew I'd find you!

832
00:54:00,480 --> 00:54:02,639
♪ Oh, here in the sea

833
00:54:02,640 --> 00:54:04,679
♪ Just Owl and me

834
00:54:04,680 --> 00:54:06,919
♪ We're going home for tea ♪

835
00:54:09,920 --> 00:54:13,679
Um... Are you sure this is the way?
Don't worry!

836
00:54:13,680 --> 00:54:16,159
I have an EXCELLENT
sense of direction!

837
00:54:16,160 --> 00:54:17,840
Nearly there!

838
00:54:23,040 --> 00:54:26,479
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!

839
00:54:26,480 --> 00:54:28,239
Just as I thought.

840
00:54:28,240 --> 00:54:30,760
The pool room. We're getting closer!

841
00:54:31,800 --> 00:54:33,840
Do you hear that?

842
00:54:34,640 --> 00:54:36,960
It's coming from outside.

843
00:54:40,360 --> 00:54:42,519
Stay down!

844
00:54:42,520 --> 00:54:43,999
What did you say?

845
00:54:44,000 --> 00:54:46,639
Um... Watch it... Um...

846
00:54:46,640 --> 00:54:48,919
Yeah, because, uh... that sound...

847
00:54:48,920 --> 00:54:50,879
sounds really suspicious.
Yeah...

848
00:54:50,880 --> 00:54:52,719
- Yeah.
- Yeah.
- So, yeah, be careful.
- Hm.

849
00:54:52,720 --> 00:54:54,879
Did they see you?

850
00:54:54,880 --> 00:54:58,600
Eh... Eh... I-I don't think so!

851
00:55:00,600 --> 00:55:04,200
Nearly there!

852
00:55:05,360 --> 00:55:06,960
Are we at the dam?

853
00:55:07,960 --> 00:55:10,879
Uh...
# They all adore me

854
00:55:10,880 --> 00:55:12,959
♪ They're wishing my voice

855
00:55:12,960 --> 00:55:15,279
♪ When I sing, my heart

856
00:55:15,280 --> 00:55:17,799
♪ Si-i-i-ings...

857
00:55:21,040 --> 00:55:23,240
A-A-A-Ah!

858
00:55:30,920 --> 00:55:32,920
Wha-a-a-at?!

859
00:55:33,880 --> 00:55:37,399
Oh, no! Beaver's bound
to have heard that!

860
00:55:37,400 --> 00:55:40,439
Oh, my muscles...
are all confused.

861
00:55:40,440 --> 00:55:42,319
They don't know the way to go.

862
00:55:42,320 --> 00:55:45,679
Well, perhaps they just need
a little bit of help, Prickly Pig.

863
00:55:45,680 --> 00:55:48,239
Yeah, bit of help from some rats!
- Pi-rats!
- Yeah.

864
00:55:48,240 --> 00:55:50,440
Why would you help us?

865
00:55:51,480 --> 00:55:53,959
We offered to help before,
didn't we, Prickly Pig?

866
00:55:53,960 --> 00:55:57,399
Yeah, 'course we did! Remember, with
- your dyke?
- Yeah! With your dyke!

867
00:55:57,400 --> 00:55:59,479
But if you don't need our help...

868
00:55:59,480 --> 00:56:02,239
No, if you don't want-You know,
we know when we're not wanted...

869
00:56:02,240 --> 00:56:04,959
Can you help? Please?
Sure!

870
00:56:04,960 --> 00:56:07,839
Prickly Pig, of course, we can help.
Why didn't you ask before?!

871
00:56:07,840 --> 00:56:09,799
He should've just asked,
shouldn't he?

872
00:56:14,520 --> 00:56:17,240
Oh! No-o-o-o!

873
00:56:31,240 --> 00:56:34,880
Wait! What did I tell you?
Oh, no, he's coming!

874
00:56:36,240 --> 00:56:38,000
Hurry! Run!

875
00:56:42,320 --> 00:56:44,319
We have to lift the platform!...

876
00:56:44,320 --> 00:56:47,679
Um... Oh, which lever was it?
Hurry!

877
00:56:47,680 --> 00:56:50,119
Beaver is getting closer.

878
00:56:50,120 --> 00:56:52,240
That's it!

879
00:56:55,120 --> 00:56:57,719
What happened!?! Why did it stop?

880
00:56:59,920 --> 00:57:02,200
What now?

881
00:57:03,520 --> 00:57:05,879
There's plenty more
where that came from!

882
00:57:05,880 --> 00:57:08,080
Right in the kisser!

883
00:57:10,680 --> 00:57:13,439
Yeah! Bull's eye!

884
00:57:13,440 --> 00:57:16,560
Ha! Ho-doh! Ho! Hi-ya-a-a-ah!

885
00:57:17,400 --> 00:57:20,360
How do we get out!?!
Ah! I've got it!

886
00:57:21,400 --> 00:57:23,399
Oi! Where did you get
that water gun?

887
00:57:23,400 --> 00:57:26,400
Yeah, where did you get that gun?
- Tusk!
- He's gone and nicked it.

888
00:57:27,280 --> 00:57:30,599
We have to dislodge the railing!

889
00:57:30,600 --> 00:57:32,919
We're running out of stuff to throw!

890
00:57:32,920 --> 00:57:34,879
Yah!

891
00:57:34,880 --> 00:57:36,880
Great! Now put it down over there!

892
00:57:38,720 --> 00:57:42,359
Oh, you clever...!
A bridge to the waterslide!

893
00:57:42,360 --> 00:57:44,600
Hare, you are a genius!

894
00:57:55,320 --> 00:57:59,119
I'm coming to get you! Wo-o-o-ow!

895
00:58:01,160 --> 00:58:03,559
He's not very good
at hide and seek, is he?

896
00:58:05,600 --> 00:58:07,680
Wa-a-a-ah!

897
00:58:10,960 --> 00:58:13,920
It's still too far up.
How do we get there?

898
00:58:15,840 --> 00:58:19,240
Don't touch that! That's my
rope! I stole it fair and square.

899
00:58:22,240 --> 00:58:24,599
Where are they?

900
00:58:28,040 --> 00:58:30,839
Ah, it won't stick!

901
00:58:30,840 --> 00:58:33,639
Got it!
Woo-hoo!

902
00:58:33,640 --> 00:58:36,359
- Owl!
- Mermaid!

903
00:58:36,360 --> 00:58:38,399
I have to find them.

904
00:58:38,400 --> 00:58:40,320
They've got to be here somewhere.

905
00:58:46,120 --> 00:58:49,959
Jack, is this the rope
I used to tie up our raft?

906
00:58:51,480 --> 00:58:53,799
Oh, no!

907
00:58:53,800 --> 00:58:57,039
It's too far to swim.
The speedboat!

908
00:58:57,040 --> 00:58:59,159
There's too many of us!

909
00:58:59,160 --> 00:59:00,719
Way too many of us.
We have to try!

910
00:59:00,720 --> 00:59:02,599
The boat won't hold!

911
00:59:02,600 --> 00:59:04,599
No way that's going to hold!

912
00:59:04,600 --> 00:59:06,479
More gas! Hit the turbo!

913
00:59:06,480 --> 00:59:09,799
OK. Um... This button?

914
00:59:09,800 --> 00:59:11,759
No, the other button!

915
00:59:11,760 --> 00:59:14,399
No, not that one.
We never push that button.

916
00:59:14,400 --> 00:59:18,119
Let me try.
I am EXCELLENT with machines!

917
00:59:28,840 --> 00:59:31,919
Ooh!
Hm. Uh.

918
00:59:42,800 --> 00:59:46,800
So, you were leaving
without saying goodbye?

919
00:59:49,520 --> 00:59:51,439
Beaver, please...

920
00:59:51,440 --> 00:59:54,999
Let them go! I'll stay with you!
I'll do whatever you want.

921
00:59:55,000 --> 00:59:58,239
And tell you how great you are,
every day.

922
00:59:58,240 --> 01:00:00,759
If you stay, I'll stay, too.

923
01:00:00,760 --> 01:00:02,919
I am not leaving you again...

924
01:00:02,920 --> 01:00:05,799
No, Hare! Go and find a dry spot.

925
01:00:05,800 --> 01:00:09,079
Build a nice new den, a den
that you'll love like your old den.

926
01:00:09,080 --> 01:00:12,679
I know that your den is
the most important thing to you.

927
01:00:12,680 --> 01:00:14,759
Oh, Fox.

928
01:00:14,760 --> 01:00:17,479
The most important thing
to me is you.

929
01:00:19,440 --> 01:00:22,839
All of you. I'm staying.

930
01:00:22,840 --> 01:00:24,719
Aw!
I'll stay.

931
01:00:24,720 --> 01:00:27,999
Me, too!
- I'll stay, too!
- Me, too!

932
01:00:28,000 --> 01:00:30,519
If the prickly pig stays,
then we're gonna stay, too.

933
01:00:30,520 --> 01:00:32,519
Yeah, we love the prickly pig,.
We're staying.

934
01:00:32,520 --> 01:00:36,199
So... you're willing
to give up everything

935
01:00:36,200 --> 01:00:38,519
for a miserable life in captivity?

936
01:00:38,520 --> 01:00:42,239
Under my terrifying,
yet admirable power?

937
01:00:42,240 --> 01:00:44,479
But why?

938
01:00:44,480 --> 01:00:46,359
Because...

939
01:00:46,360 --> 01:00:48,440
Because we have something stronger.

940
01:00:49,760 --> 01:00:53,519
Friendship.
That's right.
Yes, we are... we are all friends.

941
01:00:53,520 --> 01:00:55,840
We are friends. That's what we are.
I see.

942
01:01:18,520 --> 01:01:21,080
I bet you didn't see
that one coming, huh?

943
01:01:21,920 --> 01:01:24,079
Why did you do that?

944
01:01:24,080 --> 01:01:26,599
Ah, well...

945
01:01:26,600 --> 01:01:30,039
because I realised...
by looking at you all...

946
01:01:30,040 --> 01:01:31,920
I understand now that...

947
01:01:33,320 --> 01:01:35,959
...OK, what I want to say is...

948
01:01:35,960 --> 01:01:39,320
I thought
that being admired was great.

949
01:01:40,320 --> 01:01:44,279
But it must be much greater...
to have friends.

950
01:01:44,280 --> 01:01:47,720
- - Ah.
- Oh.
- Love you, Beaver.
- That's true.
- That's lovely.

951
01:01:48,560 --> 01:01:51,480
Well... so long!

952
01:01:53,040 --> 01:01:55,479
Here, Boss, wait! Wait a minute.
Yeah, hang on, Boss!

953
01:01:55,480 --> 01:01:58,519
We can't leave him like that,
can we? We'll come with you, Boss.

954
01:01:58,520 --> 01:02:00,999
Yeah, no, we'll come with you cos,
after all, we like water.

955
01:02:01,000 --> 01:02:04,079
You know, like you do, Boss.
Yeah, we quite like you, really.

956
01:02:04,080 --> 01:02:06,599
No... No more boss-stuff.

957
01:02:06,600 --> 01:02:08,640
We're friends.

958
01:02:09,920 --> 01:02:12,679
Wait! I have an idea.

959
01:02:12,680 --> 01:02:15,200
Why don't you come with us?

960
01:02:16,360 --> 01:02:18,319
Our forest is big enough!

961
01:02:18,320 --> 01:02:20,759
We even have a small lake
where you can live.

962
01:02:20,760 --> 01:02:23,439
Near us! Your new friends.

963
01:02:23,440 --> 01:02:25,039
Yes!

964
01:02:25,040 --> 01:02:27,719
Friends?

965
01:02:27,720 --> 01:02:30,119
O-O-O-Oh...

966
01:02:30,120 --> 01:02:33,399
...of course! My new friend!

967
01:02:37,680 --> 01:02:40,439
Let's go home!

968
01:02:56,480 --> 01:02:58,520
Ooh!

969
01:02:59,560 --> 01:03:02,000
Ah!

970
01:03:03,360 --> 01:03:06,479
Ah, home sweet home.

971
01:03:06,480 --> 01:03:09,080
Look at all the dirt!

972
01:03:18,480 --> 01:03:21,359
Hm. Hm.
Hm.

973
01:03:26,760 --> 01:03:29,879
Oh, look at that.
Perfect fit, thanks.

974
01:03:29,880 --> 01:03:33,479
Yeah, that looks good, that.
Mermaid! We're ready.

975
01:03:33,480 --> 01:03:35,600
Let's go.

976
01:03:36,520 --> 01:03:38,520
Come on.

977
01:03:42,080 --> 01:03:44,960
Oh... Oh, Jack!

978
01:03:45,840 --> 01:03:48,079
What the...?!

979
01:03:48,080 --> 01:03:51,159
O-O-O-Oh!

980
01:03:51,160 --> 01:03:54,079
There!

981
01:03:54,080 --> 01:03:56,119
Now, don't worry.

982
01:03:56,120 --> 01:03:58,920
We're all safe and snug now.

983
01:04:00,360 --> 01:04:01,880
Hi, Seal!

984
01:04:03,600 --> 01:04:06,519
Just wanted to drop off
some things before we hit home.

985
01:04:06,520 --> 01:04:08,279
It's on the house.

986
01:04:08,280 --> 01:04:11,279
Oh, thank you, Seal!

987
01:04:11,280 --> 01:04:14,160
We have something for you as well.

988
01:04:16,440 --> 01:04:18,800
I made them myself.

989
01:04:22,600 --> 01:04:24,399
Do you... like them?

990
01:04:24,400 --> 01:04:26,559
I love them!

991
01:04:26,560 --> 01:04:28,599
Thank you, friend.

992
01:04:28,600 --> 01:04:31,439
Oh!
Party time!

993
01:04:31,440 --> 01:04:33,480
I love a party!

994
01:04:34,720 --> 01:04:36,160
Thank you!

995
01:04:37,240 --> 01:04:39,959
Looks delicious!

996
01:04:39,960 --> 01:04:41,999
They are really tasty!
Oh!

997
01:04:42,000 --> 01:04:44,119
Oh, way to go, Hare!

998
01:04:44,120 --> 01:04:46,840
# We are friends!

999
01:04:47,760 --> 01:04:50,240
♪ We are friends!

1000
01:04:51,080 --> 01:04:53,720
♪ We are friends!

1001
01:04:54,520 --> 01:04:56,840
♪ We are friends!

1002
01:04:57,880 --> 01:05:00,639
♪ We are best friends!

1003
01:05:00,640 --> 01:05:03,240
♪ Much better
than second best friends

1004
01:05:04,480 --> 01:05:06,720
♪ We are friends

1005
01:05:07,920 --> 01:05:09,999
♪ We are friends

1006
01:05:10,000 --> 01:05:11,919
♪ You know
We are all friends together!...

1007
01:05:11,920 --> 01:05:14,519
Oh... Look! It's the Prickly Pig!
Aye, he can sing, can't he?

1008
01:05:14,520 --> 01:05:18,159
Well, yeah, what he lacks in talent,
he makes up for in enthusiasm.

1009
01:05:18,160 --> 01:05:20,319
♪ We are friends

1010
01:05:20,320 --> 01:05:22,359
♪ We're going to be friends
to the end...

1011
01:05:22,360 --> 01:05:24,439
To the end of what?
I don't know...

1012
01:05:24,440 --> 01:05:26,959
Maybe friends
to the end of the movie.

1013
01:05:26,960 --> 01:05:28,999
Oh! It's coming up soon!

1014
01:05:29,000 --> 01:05:33,919
It's coming up...
# No-o-o-ow!...

1015
01:05:33,920 --> 01:05:36,520
I am really the best singer.

1016
01:05:38,280 --> 01:05:40,319
Well, I tell you what
I do like a happy ending,

1017
01:05:40,320 --> 01:05:43,399
and this is a happy ending.
It seems to be a happy ending, yeah!

1018
01:05:43,400 --> 01:05:45,759
Everyone seems very pleased
with the way it's turned out.

1019
01:05:45,760 --> 01:05:49,359
Where everything, all the pegs,
are fitting into the right holes.
Yeah, it's very good!

1020
01:05:49,360 --> 01:05:51,599
I would watch this.
I would watch this as well.

1021
01:05:51,600 --> 01:05:53,759
Yeah, I'm gonna watch it.
I'll watch your bit.

1022
01:05:53,760 --> 01:05:57,639
I won't watch my bit. It's hard
- to watch your own bit.
- No! I'll watch
your bit cos you're my friend.

1023
01:05:57,640 --> 01:06:00,679
- Yeah, I'm your best friend.
- You are.
Do you want to go on holiday?

1024
01:06:00,680 --> 01:06:02,880
# We are friends!

1025
01:06:04,000 --> 01:06:06,440
♪ We are friends!

1026
01:06:07,360 --> 01:06:11,839
♪ We are frie-ie-ie-iends! ♪

1027
01:07:17,440 --> 01:07:20,999
# The Beaver! The Beaver!

1028
01:07:21,000 --> 01:07:23,560
♪ The Beaver, Beaver!...

1029
01:08:13,200 --> 01:08:16,719
♪ The Beaver! The Beaver!

1030
01:08:16,720 --> 01:08:19,359
♪ The Beaver, Beaver! ♪
